<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Maijamaa</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is a virtual proof that I&apos;m awesome</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>the beauty within</title>
        <description>
          
          lilac and sands palms and groove my flames falter the story goes thus how time flies and how we go from a smile to existential dichotomy and not know from whence it came life like a vending machine on and on, it spins into existence, a whirlwind that sweeps you...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-the-beauty-within/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-the-beauty-within/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>prance like an kangaroo</title>
        <description>
          
          in this small world of mine where crystals beam and melody flickers i have come a long way to be availed just the pittance to decipher when the birds sing for joy and when they cry for freedom for i have done all but defeat the gods that i still...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-prance-like-an-kangaroo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-prance-like-an-kangaroo/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>loving may</title>
        <description>
          
          it’s april again and my mind like the sun has been shadowed by the thought of you, the eclipse above me but my self-image dwindle always in constant doubt of where my true feeling lies for one, in affair, i go unnoticed if this is what love entails i seek...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-loving-may/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-loving-may/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>can i talk to you for a moment</title>
        <description>
          
          do we still talk like we used to like we ought to if there was a yardstick for that these days, i speak and i listen you speak and you listen a monologue stricken can we ever get a dialogue when we only listen to ourselves can we ever push...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-can-i-talk-to-you-for-a-moment/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-can-i-talk-to-you-for-a-moment/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>a scavenger was here</title>
        <description>
          
          residues of a dead fantasy hopes of the hopeless for dreams once foretold, by her fountainhead aloof, hands astride, she stood about ten meters afar her loot she turns left and mutters i have trodden this road before and here too as she turns right. the path before her still...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-a-scavenger-was-here/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-06-01-a-scavenger-was-here/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My first tech blog</title>
        <description>
          
          Welcome to my first tech blog. Thank you Unreleased version BREAKING CHANGE: Allow changing the order of the social network links that appear in the footer (#1152) BREAKING CHANGE: google-scholar social network link no longer requires the prefix citations?user=; if you previously set this parameter, it needs to be updated...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-02-26-My-first-tech-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-02-26-My-first-tech-blog/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample blog post to learn markdown tips</title>
        <description>
          There&apos;s lots to learn! - 
          This is a demo post to show you how to write blog posts with markdown. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/tables/etc.I also encourage you to look at the code that...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-sample-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-sample-markdown/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
        <description>
          Excerpt from Soulshaping by Jeff Brown - 
          Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
